A Guide to the Pioneer America Society Records, 1929-1984 (bulk 1968-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Subject files, 1937-1983 (bulk 1970-1975)
  - Help Encourage Landmark Preservation, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Heritage Press, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Historic American Buildings Survey, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Historic Landmarks Search Project, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Historic Preservation, 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Historic Zoning, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - History, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - History publishers, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - House moving, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Horses, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Hotels, Nd (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Houses, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Humor, Nd (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Hurricanes, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Indians, 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Inventory, Blanks, Nd (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Ironwork, Ornamental, Nd (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - James River and Kanawha Canal Parks, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Kansas Historical Society, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Kiwanis Club, 1967-1975 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Koster Expedition, 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Land use, 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Lebanese peddlers, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Lee family, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Legends, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Legislation, Virginia, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, Vicki, Nd (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Library of Congress, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Life along the rails, Nd (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Lighthouse, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Lime kilns, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Living History Farms, Bulletin, 1971-1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Living History Farms, Publications, 1967-1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local history, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Log houses, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Lumber, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Lynchburg Historical Society, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Machinery, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Madison, James, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Mad stones, 1953-1963 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Maps and indexes, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Maps, Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Mass transit, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - McCall, Tom, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - McCarthy, Colman, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Mennonites, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mills, New England, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mills, Virginia, Nd (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Money raising, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Montana State Society, Nd (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Moonshine, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Nails, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - National Capital Historical Museum of Transportaion, Inc. 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - National Colonial Farm, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - National Geographic Magazine, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - National Heritage, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - National Parks, Nd (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - National Railway Historical Society, Inc. 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - National Register, 1968-1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1970-1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Nature Conservancy, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Negroes, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Negro History, 1953-1970 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Northern Neck of Virginia Historical Society, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Northern Virginia Center School, University of Virginia, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Nostalgia, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Office of Archeology, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Old Mills Society, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Old Schwamb Mill, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Oral history, 1970-1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Orchard grass, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Out of doors, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Pearson, Drew, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Canal Society, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Folklore Society, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Historical Junto, 1971-1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - People, 1968-1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Photography, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Piedmont Environmental Council, 1973-1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Piedmont Virginian, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Pollution, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Population, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Postal permit, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Potomac Appalachian Trail Club, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Potomac River Basin, 1970-1979 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Preservation, 1969-1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Preservation Action, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Preservation properties, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Preservation Resource Group, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Projects, Nd (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Publications, Complete Set, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Publications in progress, Nd (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Railroads, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Railroads, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Railroad stations, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Railway mail, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rappahannock Defense Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Realtors, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Recycling, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Restoration, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Revolving Fund Conference, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Wild Rice Men, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rip Off, Big, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Rivers, 1968-1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Roads, 1968-1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Royall, Anne, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Scheel, Eugene, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Schools, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Send literature, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Service League of Northern Virginia, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Shakers, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Sheep shearing, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Shenandoah Valley Folklore Society, 1968-1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Shipjack, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Slaves, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Smithsonian, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Society for Historical Archaeology, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Society for Industrial Archeology, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Society of Architectural Historians, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Solar energy, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Sorghum, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Stagecoaches, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Steam engine, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Steam turbines, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Stoves, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Strip mining, 1972-1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Survey of North American Culture, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Tapes, transcriptions, etc., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Tinsmithing, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Titles, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Tobacco barns, Nd (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Tools, Old, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Trains, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Transportation, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Trees, 1971-1983 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Tri State Trader, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Trolleys, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - United States Marine Corps, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - United States, Villages and Small towns, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - University microfilms, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - University of Virginia, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Vandalism, 1967-1973 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Vernacular architecture, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Victorian architecture, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Victorian society, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Virginia, Department of Highways, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Folklore Society, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Historic Landmarks Commission, 1967-1979 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Historic Landmarks Commission, Newsletters, 1971-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Historical Society, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, Landmarks, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Virginia State Library, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Washington, George, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Washington Post, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Washington Star, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Water tanks, Nd (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Wells Fargo, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Western History Association, 1968-1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - WHA, Mailed, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - WHA, Mailing list, Nd (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Westerners Foundation, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Wilderness, 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Wind, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Windmills, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Yellowstone Park, Nd (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Zeppelins, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Zeppelin, Hindenburg, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Zoning, 1973-1977 (Box 20, Folder 21)